<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Lonavala Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Category name for phrases [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_lake">Lake/Dams</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary places for colors [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_fort">Forts</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary places for numbers [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_cave">Caves</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary places for family members [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_other">Other</string>

    <!--  -->
    <string name="tungarli_lake">It is great fun even for adventure enthusiasts as one can trek
        through the nearby areas. The Tungarli Dam is built alongside Tungarli lake in the region
        of Rajmachi. The dam helps in the irrigation facilities of the region.
        One can also camp alongside the lake after an adventurous trekking trip
        making it a soulful experience.</string>
    <string name="pawana_lake">At a distance of 15 km from Lonavala Railway Station and 10 km from
        Lohagad Fort, Pawna Lake is an artificial lake formed by water of Pawna dam.
        Situated towards the outskirts of Lonavala, this lake is one of the top
        Lonavala tourist places.</string>
    <string name="bushi_dam">This is one of the most popular spots in Maharashtra. People from
        all over the state, especially the weekend travelers flock to this place
        for a relaxed time.</string>
    <string name="valvan_dam">Lush greenery and calm surroundings make up the Valvan Dam, which
        is a near perfect evening outing spot, near Lonavala. The Kundali River is the one which
        feeds the dam, and it in return supplies the water to the Khopoli Hydroelectricity
        Water Plant at the foothills of Sahyadri.</string>
    <string name="rajmachi_fort">Midway between Lonavala and Khandala is a fort by the name of
        Rajmachi Fort, a prominent landmark that watches over some of the most
        breathtakingly beautiful and wide sceneries of the region.</string>
    <string name="lohagad_fort">This is one of many forts of Chhatrapati Shivaji, adorned with
        elements and styles of Maharshtrian architecture. Not only the grandeur of the structure,
        but the sceneries and views all around, make it another favorite of all its visitors.
    </string>
    <string name="visapur_fort">Surrounded by a huge plateau, is a historical fort, land marking
        the lush green and dreamy mountains of Khandala. A 3-hour drive away from Mumbai, this
        one is often marked as a favorite for the monsoons.</string>
    <string name="tiger_point">This is a popular tourist point, leaving tourists in awe with the
        wondrous view from over 650m. The echo point is a major fascination. During the monsoon,
        the waterfall here, also attracts many. It has got it's name from its appearance - like
        that of a tiger leaping into the valley.
    </string>
    <string name="imagica">A world class entertainment park, Imagica Adlabs is a one of its kind
        destination picnic spot with plethora of entertainment options.
        Located on Mumbai-Pune Expressway, this theme park is one of the latest
        additions in the list of Mumbai's entrainment hubs.</string>
    <string name="aamby_valley">A one of its kind, this place is known for its irreplaceable
        grandeur and plush signature features. The fountains of ecstasy, Sahyadri peaks and the
        historic Koyarigarh fort offer a spectacular view of the grand Aambey valley city.</string>
    <string name="karla_caves">The Karla Caves are reflection of mesmerizing beauty of the past
        carved and decorated with great details. The place is a paradise for history lovers and
        adventure buffs.</string>
    <string name="bhaja_cave">Believed to be the oldest Buddhist religious site in the county,
        it is declared as the national monument. The main attraction of the place are the
        22 rock-cut caves which depict various sculptures , like that of a prince in a chariot,
        a prince seated on an elephant, among others.</string>
    <string name="ekvira_temple">The Ekvira Aai Mandir is a Hindu temple located near the Karla
        Caves near Lonavala in Maharashtra, India. Here, the worship of the goddess Ekvira is
        carried on right next to the caves, once a center of Buddhism. The temple is a prime
        spot of worship for the Aagri-Koli People. </string>
    <string name="rajmachi">Rajmachi Point is located at a walking distance from The Dukes Retreat.
        This spot got its name because Rajmachi Fort of the incredible Maratha ruler Chatrapati
        Sivaji is situated opposite to this point. The point offers spectacular views of
        Rajmachi Fort, the surrounding valley and waterfalls. Rajmachi Point has a temple and a
        children's park. This is also a famous area for movie producers.</string>
</resources>
